The stakeholders for available, reliant,
利益相关方提供 依赖
and resilient systems are almost every function in a company.
而弹性系统几乎是公司的每一个功能
Your customers be able to depend on your platform to be
您的客户可以依赖您的平台
running and stable is going to be critical to your overall success.
运行和稳定对于您的整体成功至关重要
Most software platforms have service level agreements,
大多数软件平台都有服务级别协议
or SLAs, that are critical to business stakeholders.
或 SLA 对业务项目干系人至关重要
All business functions tend to be concerned with
所有业务功能都倾向于关注
a company's SLAs as they have widespread impact.
公司的 SLA  因为它们具有广泛的影响
The business both expects its vendors to meet their SLAs,
业务双方都预计其供应商将满足其 SLA
and it is vital for a company to achieve its published SLAs,
对一家公司实现已发布的 SLA 至关重要
in order to meet contractual obligations and support customers.
以满足合同义务和支持客户